Donald Miller

Forklift operator

Fremont, CA millerdmj@gmail.com - (925) 209-1805

Efficient Forklift Driver able to operate a wide range of warehouse equipment in a safe and efficient manner.r Trained in all aspects of shipment inspections and transportation. Versed in using scanners and warehouse management systems (WMS) to promote safe and on-time shipment and delivery. Enthusiastic about working in team-based settings to accomplish challenging objectives. 20+ years of equipment operation experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Production Worker

Y C Cable - Fremont, CA -

April 2018 to October 2018

Examined incoming materials and compared to documentation. Assembled products according to standardized procedures. Organized work to meet demanding production goals. Set up and verified the functionality of safety equipment.

Forklift Operator

PABCO Gypsum - Fremont, CA -

March 2016 to November 2017

Inspected product load for accuracy and safely transported it around the warehouse. Placed loads in the optimal manner to maximize efficiency of work. Worked in a team environment to maintain high levels of productivity. Handled multiple tasks simultaneously to maximize work efficiency. Coordinated with other lift truck drivers and production personnel to process orders efficiently.

Order Picker

Synnex Corp - Fremont, CA -

January 2014 to September 2016

Safely operated all warehouse equipment, including forklifts and pallet jacks.

Utilized an RF scanner to pick items to the proper bins.

Maintained accurate stock records and schedules.

Led warehouse improvement initiatives to advance operational efficiencies.

Detail-oriented Order Picker with experience working in various large warehouse environments. Seeking a similar role where outstanding packing skills and a strong commitment to safety will be valued.

EDUCATION

High School Diploma

Concordia College - Moorhead, MN

SKILLS

FORKLIFT (1 year), SHIPPING, SHIPPING AND RECEIVING, ASSEMBLY, ASSEMBLY LINE, General Labor

CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

Certified Forklift Operator

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS

Assembly protocols Machinery operation
Quality assurance Microsoft applications skills
Material handling expert Production procedures
Extremely quick learner Assembly line production
Interpersonal skills Forklift Operation
Shipping and Receiving Packaging